math.com 2017-12-02

# Math.com Privacy Policy

|  | **Resources** |   
---|---|---  
|  **·  **Cool Tools  
**·  **Formulas & Tables  
**·  **References  
**·  **Test Preparation  
**·  **Study Tips  
**·  **Wonders of Math  
   
| **Search** |   
| 

Custom Search 

   | 

Privacy Policy For Math.com

(last updated March 9, 2016)  
At Math.com your privacy is important to us. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. Math.com's policy regarding use of your individual identifying information or other information supplied to us or collected during your visit(s) to the Math.com website covers the following areas: 

  * Information Gathering
  * Opt-Out/Removal from Database
  * Children's Guidelines
  * Questions/Comments

**Information Gathering  
**1\. Math.com uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. The Math.com registration form requires users to give contact information (such as their name and e-mail address) and demographic information (such as their age and zip code). Such information may be used to tailor the visitor's experience at the Site and display selected content that Math.com believes the visitor may be interested in. 

2\. The Site uses an order form for visitors to request information, products and services. This form will collect the visitor's contact information (such as their e-mail address and name) and financial information (such as their credit card number). Contact information derived from the order form is used to deliver products and services ordered by Math.com customers, and to otherwise contact such customers. Financial information that is collected is used to bill Math.com customers for products and services.

[Back to Top] 

3\. **Opt-Out/Removal from Database  
**The Site gives its users the following options for (i) deleting their Math.com registration, contact and financial information from the Math.com database, (ii) discontinuing communications from Math.com or (iii) discontinuing receipt of Math.com products or services: send email to: [optout@LOFFS.com](mailto:optout@LOFFS.com)

[Back to Top]

4\. **Children's Guidelines**  
The Site is intended for use by children and adults for educational purposes. Math.com recognizes the importance of privacy with respect to children's information and will therefore follow guidelines intended to uphold such privacy. 

> **To this end, Math.com will NOT:**

  * Collect contact information without seeking prior parental consent or parental notification, which may include an opportunity for the parent to limit use of the information and participation in the activity;

  * Collect personally identifiable off-line contact information without seeking prior parental consent;

  * Distribute to third parties any personally identifiable contact information without seeking prior parental consent; 

  * Provide the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without seeking prior parental consent; 

  * Entice the user with the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity in order to divulge more information than necessary to participate in the activity.

[Back to Top]

**Questions/Comments**  
If you have any questions about the Math.com Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your experience with Math.com, please contact the Math.com Privacy Team at [privacy@LOFFS.com](mailto:privacy@LOFFS.com). We can also be reached via our corporate owner, namely:

Leap of Faith Financial Services Inc.  
34 Burnfield Avenue  
Toronto, Ontario, Canada  
tel: 416-588-0269 fax: 416-588-5641

* **Third Party Cookies**
  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser or use web beacons to collect information. You can manage your cookies preferences through the relevant mechanisms in your web browser (see the preferences or options menus). Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
* **Third Party Advertising and Content**
  
Third parties (including us and other advertisers) may serve content and advertisements, collect information directly from users, and place or recognize cookies in connection with this site. These third parties may also collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information, including phone number). Google may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Google Account. When you use a location-enabled service, third parties may collect and process information about your actual location, such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device. They may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and mobile towers.

If you would like to review the privacy policies of our third party advertisers and/or analytics, please visit [Google](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html), [AOL Advertising](http://privacy.aol.com/) and, [Commission Junction](http://www.cj.com/privacy.html). You can learn more about how Google products use your data by visiting [this page](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/). 

* **Behavioral Advertising and Content**
  
Third parties (including us and other advertisers) may serve content and advertisements, collect information directly from users, and place or recognize cookies in connection with this site for behavioral advertising. To opt out, visit [the NAI opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  |    |
